Eric Ruthig

Avon, IN 46123 contact@reorientbodywork.com 7732254420

I have been involved in the field of Massage Therapy for the last seven years as a Licensed Massage Therapist (IL) and a Certified Massage Therapist (IN). I have changed gears and am currently entering the field of Web Development having recently completed a course.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Certified Massage Therapist

Indy Massage Company - Indianapolis, IN November 2016 to Present

Responsibilities include performing massage therapy and room cleaning.

Licensed Massage Therapist

Soothe Inc - Chicago, IL April 2016 to Present

In home massage

Licensed Massage Therapist

Sauganash Wellness Center - Chicago, IL June 2014 to September 2016

Responsibilities included performing massage therapy and room cleaning.

Licensed Massage Therapist

Cleise Brazilian Day Spa - Chicago, IL May 2015 to May 2016

Responsibilities included performing massage therapy and room cleaning.

Education

Certificate

Pacific College of Oriental Medicine - Chicago, IL 2013

Covenant Christian High School - Indianapolis, IN

Skills

• ABMP Member #1062780

- Spanish (fluent)
- Hot Stone Certified
- Cupping Certified
- Anatomy Knowledge
- Trigger Point Therapy
- English
- Physiology Knowledge
- Thai Massage
- HTML (Less than 1 year)
- CSS (Less than 1 year)
- JavaScript (Less than 1 year)

Certifications and Licenses

Massage Therapy License

Massage Therapy License

Massage Therapy License

Massage Therapy License